前情提要
REBEKAH: Previously on The Originals...
这座城市曾经是我的家
This town was my home once.
我不在的日子里
马赛尔得到了我想要的一切
And in my absence,
Marcel has got everything I ever wanted.
我要夺回来
I want it back.
我在此宣誓效忠于你
I hereby pledge my
allegiance to you.
你现在拥有我的王国
You have the keys to my kingdom.
你将再一次为他而放弃我，是吗？
You're choosing him over me,
aren't you, again?
所有爱尼克劳斯的人得到的回报
The only reward anyone
ever gets for loving Niklaus,
只有痛苦和死亡
-is suffering and death.
-(SOBBlNG)
尼克劳斯，她怀了你的孩子
Niklaus, the girl is carrying your child.
你跟我走，小狼
You're coming with me, little wolf.
我现在在万能克劳斯的保护下
I've been deemed under
protection by the almighty Klaus.
我想是时候让我侄女卡蜜离开这里了
I believe it is time for my niece, Cami,
to leave town.
离开纽奥良
忘记所有一切
Leave New Orleans.
Forget everything.
我认识你吗？
Do I know you?
你被魅惑了
You've been compelled.
没事的，我能解除你的魅惑
It's okay. I can fix you.
(1751年 路易斯安那领地）
几世纪以来，人们来到纽奥良
寻找新的开始
REBEKAH: For centuries, people have come
to New Orleans looking for a fresh start,
希望能找到财富、奇遇，甚至是爱情
hoping to find fortune,
adventure, even love.
从法国来的年轻社交名媛获得许诺
Young society women, imported from
France with the promise of marrying
能嫁给体面的纽奥良绅士
就像传说中的木匣女孩
a proper New Orleans gentleman.
Like the legendary Casket Girls.
打扰一下，先生
还有多久才能到总督府呢？
她们并不知道等待着她们的男人
不仅毫不体面
Little did they know that the men who
awaited them were far from proper.
而且一点也不绅士
And not at all gentle.
让她们出来，我们要见女人
MAN: Get them out.
We want to see the women.
快出来
Come out here.
我们要女人
-(SCREAMlNG)
-We want the women.
别害怕，小羔羊
Oh, there, there, little lambs.
坏男人都不在了
All the bad men have gone away.
你们已经安全了，请原谅刚才的骚乱
(SPEAKlNG FORElGN LANGUAGE)
我们女生必须团结起来
Us girls have got to stick together.
你们有什么要带走的吗？
好
了
Now, is there anything
you want to take with you?
片名：创始吸血鬼（第一季）
剧名：木匣女孩
木匣女孩的故事流传至今
REBEKAH: The Casket Girls'
legend lives on.
如今以纽奥良特有的形式庆贺
Now celebrated in typical
New Orleans fashion...
穿上时尚华服，点缀一些超能力
主演：约瑟夫摩根
...with stylish costumes
and supernatural flair.
每年一度的节日提醒着大家
It's a yearly reminder of how women
女人如何被自私男人压迫
主演：丹尼尔吉利斯
can be oppressed by selfish men...
以及她们勇敢地为自己而战
最终获得胜利
...and how they can triumph when brave
enough to fight for themselves.
天啊，好痛！
Oh, God, it hurts!
抱歉，卡蜜
这是解除克劳斯魅惑的唯一办法
I'm sorry, Cami. It's the only way
to break all of Klaus' compulsion.
相信我，我知道这有多痛
你会没事的
Believe me, I know what it's like.
You're okay.
那个，你写的这些纸条
And, hey,
all these notes that you made?
（别相信克劳斯）
这种记忆法很赞
干得好
It's very Memento of you.
Nice work.
我们已经忙了一整晚
We've been at this all night.
我不明白我究竟发生了什么事
主演：克莱儿荷特
I don't understand what's happening to me.
这一切我都不明白
主演：克莱儿荷特
I don't understand any of this.
但你会明白的
But you will.
我会为你找回一切被夺走的记忆
I will unlock every stolen memory,
解除一切吸血鬼
主演：菲比托金
undo every piece of mind control
曾对你进行的精神控制
主演：菲比托金
that any vampire
has ever done to you.
结束后，你就能明白这一切
When I am done,
you will understand all of it,
那时你也就自由了
and you'll be free.
如果你想，我可以停下来
主演：查尔斯麦可戴维斯
I can stop if you want me to.
不，别停下来
主演：查尔斯麦可戴维斯
No. Don't stop.
我想记起一切
主演：丹妮耶拉皮纳达
I want to remember everything.
主演：莉雅派普斯
主演：丹妮儿坎贝尔
你需要帮忙吗？
Would you like some help?
你可能得用上你全部的吸血鬼力量
You might need to use
all your vampire strength.
让我来吧
Allow me.
谢谢
Thanks.
没有几个木匣女孩是大着肚子的吧
Not too many pregnant
Casket Girls, I guess.
我觉得你很美
但我得…
I think you look lovely.
Only I would--
我知道，得把那奇怪的狼人胎记遮住
I know, keep the
freaky werewolf birthmark covered.
我不认为这里的．乌合之众
Well, I don't suspect
any of the riffraff here
会胆敢伤害你
would dare lay a hand on you,
明知你在我们家族的保护之下
制片：兰斯安德森
knowing that you're
under the protection of my family.
不过还是小心为妙
Still, we shouldn't take any chances.
被搞大了肚子且无处可去
All knocked up and nowhere to go.
这样吧
如果你想参加今晚的节日庆典
You know, if you wanted
to attend the festivities tonight,
我很乐意带你去
I'd be more than willing to take you.
你和克劳斯现在闹得那么僵
制片：邦妮怀斯
You and Klaus are
barely on speaking terms.
还是不要平生事端了，对吧？
Let's not rock the boat, okay?
当然
Of course.
以利亚
Elijah.
能帮我一下吗？
Do you mind?
当然
Not at all.
编剧：查理察尔邦尼
蜜雪儿侃洛戴斯
导演：杰西瓦恩
平庸，沉闷，丑爆
Dull, dreary, hideous.
是在说衣服呢，还是另有所指？
Talking about the clothes,
or something else?
怎么，缺乏安全感吗？
Why, feeling insecure?
这个节日可以说是因我而创
This festival might as well
be in my honor.
我需要一身合适的衣服，别烦我
I need a proper costume,
so bugger off.
- 蕾贝卡
- 别碰我
-Rebekah.
-Don't.
你已经做出了选择
You made your choice.
你和克劳斯又成为好朋友了
You and Klaus are best friends again.
你已经放弃了动我的权利
You've relinquished
your right to touch me.
会是谁打来的呢？
I wonder who that could be.
什么事？
(PHONE BEEPS)
What's up?
出了点问题
Bit of an issue.
似乎我们的小鸟从笼子里飞走了
Seems our little bird
has flown the coop.
你应该会开始有如释重负的感觉
You should start to feel it,
like a weight lifting.
现在你的小纸条可就容易理解多了
And your cheat sheets are
about to make a lot more sense.
我保证，只要没人再追捕我
I promise, as soon as
the world stops hunting me,
我一定会找到日光戒指的咒语
I will find the daylight ring spell.
我明白，你现在不用烦心这事
I know.
Just don't worry about that right now.
我记得我为什么会写下这个了
I remember why I wrote this.
我找到一张1919年的照片
上面有克劳斯和马赛尔
I found a picture of
Klaus and Marcel from 1919.
克劳斯魅惑我让我和马赛尔约会
以便监视他
Klaus compelled me to go out
with Marcel, to spy on him.
他昨天告诉过我
在他让我忘记一切之前
That's what he said yesterday,
before he told me to forget.
我想起来了
I'm remembering.
我们继续解除之前的魅惑吧
Let's take you back more.
离开纽奥良
Leave New Orleans.
忘了我
Forget me.
你哥哥病了
Your brother was ill.
你没有留在这里的理由
You have no reason to stay.
就算不是神探也能看出来
You don't have to be
Sherlock Holmes to know the obvious.
我们的秘密武器逃走了
Our secret weapon has escaped.
她不会就这么走的
She wouldn't just leave.
她知道女巫在找她
She knows the witches want her back.
她的小提琴也不见了
Her violin is missing.
她应该是自愿离开的
She may have left
of her own volition.
你在阁楼和她说了什么？
What did you say to her in the attic?
她为了继续待在那里对我撒谎
She lied to my face
so she could stay up there,
以为你会帮她控制她的法力
thinking that you'd
help her control her magic.
我们怎么知道是不是你把她带走了
How do we know
that you didn't take her?
我不知道黛维娜在哪，为什么要逃跑
I have no idea where Davina is
or why she ran away.
还有你能别离我这么近吗？
Can I suggest you take a step back?
我可以保证，我绝不想
I can assure you,
I have absolutely no desire
看到那孩子受到伤害
to see that child
come into harm's way.
那个荒谬的收获祭仪式
让她吃尽了苦头
She's suffered enough
with this Harvest ritual nonsense.
你充满慈爱地说到的那个女孩
That child to whom
you refer so affectionately,
正是纽奥良最厉害的女巫
is the most powerful witch
in New Orleans.
如果她跑了，要如何阻止她摧毁我们？
If she's fled,
what's to stop her from destroying us?
事实上是摧毁我们苦心经营的一切？
In fact, destroying all we've worked for?
不
No.
如果她不是我们的朋友
就是我们的敌人
If she's not a friend to this family,
then she is our enemy.
她是我们的朋友，克劳斯
She is a friend, Klaus.
但愿如此
Well, let's hope so.
算你走运，我知道怎么把她找回来
Lucky for you,
I know how to get her back.
听我指挥
Follow my lead.
你知道尼克劳斯的作风
You know how Niklaus operates.
如果他觉得自己受到了威胁
他会变得残忍无情
If he perceives a threat,
he can become quite ruthless.
这对黛维娜来说很不妙
This would not bode well for Davina.
我不会让任何人伤害她
I'm not gonna let anybody
lay a finger on her.
我也不会
Nor will l.
听说小女巫不见了，是吗？
So the witch is missing, huh?
显然是从正门出去的
知道怎么回事吗？
Walked right out the front door.
Know anything about it?
不知道
No.
不过我确实有跟她说
那些女巫长老已经死了
Although I did tell her that
the witch elders were dead.
那些女巫想杀了她来献祭
她怎么会在意呢？
Why would she care when the witches
tried to kill her in their ritual?
我想应该是马赛尔没告诉她
I think it was more that Marcel
didn't tell her that the one thing
让她重获自由的障碍已经清除了
preventing her from being free
had been eliminated.
这么说她跑掉还是你引起的
So you are the reason she's run off.
嘿，我只是实话实说
Hey, I was just telling her the truth.
是她自己意识到他们只是利用她
She's the one who realized
they were just using her
来控制女巫
to keep their control
over the witches.
我对男子俱乐部从来就不感兴趣
Well, I've never been
a fan of the boys' club.
等着吧，以利亚会加入他们
他们三个一定合不来的
Just wait. Elijah will join them,
and the three of them will be impossible.
被女巫利用，被马赛尔蒙骗
Used by the witches,
lied to by Marcel,
被以利亚操控，被克劳斯威胁
manipulated by Elijah,
threatened by Klaus.
她就是现代版的木匣女孩
She's like a modern-day Casket Girl.
你说的是黛维娜还是你自己？
Are you talking about Davina
or yourself?
有关系吗？
Does it matter?
不管怎样，我们女生必须团结起来
Either way, us girls
have got to stick together.
抱歉打扰了
Sorry to interrupt.
打了一个小时的电话给你
Been calling you for like an hour.
我以为这样你就明白了
I thought you'd have taken the hint.
爱格妮丝死后你就一直这样浑浑噩噩的
You've been acting like this
since Agnes was killed.
可不，但能怪我吗？
Yeah. Can you blame me?
最近又没多少事可做
It's not like I have a lot
to keep me going these days.
当你随便找个大街上的人
While you've been
drowning your sorrows
来抚平内心悲痛的时候
by nailing everything that walks,
我一直在四处观察
低调行事，打探消息
I've been doing my tours,
keeping my head down and my ears open.
马赛尔的日行者正在全城上下
找一个女孩
Marcel's Daywalkers are scouring
the whole town looking for a girl,
棕发蓝眼
听来熟悉吗？
brown hair, blue eyes.
Sound familiar?
如果黛维娜没和马赛尔在一起
他就不会知道我们在使用魔法
If Davina is not with Marcel,
he won't know if we're practicing magic.
而如果我们可以找到她
一切都得以补救
And if we can actually get her back,
we can fix everything.
太阳要下山了
会有更多吸血鬼出来找人
Sun goes down,
vampire search parties quadruple.
我从她家的老房子里找到了这个
I got this from her family's old house.
应该可以施定位咒
Feel like a locator spell?
继续喝
Keep drinking.
你要让体内充满马鞭草
这样你就不会再被魅惑了
You need the vervain in your system
so you can't be compelled again.
卡蜜
你家冰箱里有人血吗？
Hey, Cami, you don't have any, like,
human blood in your fridge, do you?
怎么会有呢？来吧
For crying out loud, here.
黛维娜？
Davina?
有人在使用魔法
Someone is practicing magic.
她们在找我
They're trying to find me.
那我们必须马上离开
Then we have to run.
我现在不可能逃出法语区的
There is no way to sneak me
out of The Quarter.
每个人都在找我
By now, everyone is looking for me.
女巫、马赛尔、克劳斯
The witches, Marcel, Klaus.
- 我叔叔会有办法的
- 卡蜜
-My uncle will know what to do.
-Cami.
他得知道这里到底发生了什么事
He has to know some of what's
going on in this town, right?
- 卡蜜，别说了，他都知道
- 除非他也被魅惑了
-Cami, stop. He knows.
-Unless he's been compelled.
- 你在说什么啊？
- 他都知道
-What are you talking about?
-He knows.
他和马赛尔是一伙的
He works with Marcel.
他们算得上是朋友
我听到他们的谈话
They're practically friends.
I hear them talk.
他知道所有事情
He knows everything.
不会的
No.
如果他知道女巫对我哥哥下了咒
他会告诉我的
He would've told me if he knew
the witches put a hex on my brother.
他真的知道吗？
He knows?
卡蜜
Cami...
天啊
Oh, my God.
他知道
He knows.
你们真的该走了，现在就走
Hey, you guys seriously need to go.
Like, now.
飞机、火车、汽车，坐什么都行
Plane, train, automobile, whatever.
开我的车，就停在码头边
我传简讯告诉你它的位置
Take my car. It's parked down at
the docks, I'll text you to where.
把你的号码存进卡蜜的手机
Put your number in Cami's phone.
法语区大部分已经封锁
我们得步行
Most of the quarter is shut down
right now, we'll have to walk.
而且太阳一直不下山
And the sun is taking
forever to go down.
嘿，别哭
Hey, no tears.
答应我天一黑你就来和我们会合
Promise you'll meet us
as soon as it gets dark out.
好的，别担心我
别让他们找到你
Yeah, don't worry about me.
Just don't let them find you.
我知道克劳斯派你们跟着我
I know Klaus told you to follow me,
但你们真的有必要
跟着我去洗手间吗？
but does it really mean
you have to follow me to the bathroom?
（苏菲德弗罗来电）
给我两分钟
是我的妇产科医生
Just give me two minutes.
It's my gynecologist.
你到底要干什么？
What the hell do you want?
我知道你不信任我
I know you don't trust me.
不过你得听我说
But you need to listen.
一切即将发生变化
Everything is about to change.
黛维娜溜出来了
Davina is on the loose.
你查得很清楚是吗？
Figured that out on your own, huh?
但这跟我有什么关系呢？
Remind me again
why I should give a damn.
我需要你的帮助
好让女巫们完成收种祭
I need something from you, so that
the witches can complete the Harvest.
我凭什么要帮你们女巫获得更多力量？
On what planet would I help
you witches get more power?
你们一直在对我施咒
All you've done is
hex me left and right.
因为如果我们不完成收获祭
You'll help me because
if we don't complete the Harvest,
我们就会永远失去法力
our access to magic
will fade for good,
这对你的家族没有好处
which doesn't bode
well for your family.
你怎么知道我家族的事？
What do you know about my family?
你是新月狼族的一员
You're from the
Crescent Wolf bloodline.
马赛尔强迫一个女巫施咒
使他们只能保持狼形
Marcel forced a witch to curse them
so they'd be trapped in wolf form.
给我一个理由让我不挂电话
And I should keep
listening to you because--?
因为施咒的女巫是我的祖先
Because my bloodline
executed that curse.
你帮助我完成收获祭
我就帮你解除咒语
Help me complete the Harvest,
and I'll undo the curse for you.
但我能做什么呢？
But what can I do?
我需要一名强大女巫的遗骨来献祭
I need to consecrate the remains
of a powerful witch
以便吸取她们的法力
so I can absorb their magic.
我知道有个女巫的尸体从未被找到
I know of one whose
body was never found.
她叫莎莉丝特杜博
Her name is Celeste Dubois.
你们应该有一个共同的朋友
I believe you and she
have a friend in common.
以利亚
Elijah.
据说她死后
Story goes that when she died,
以利亚依照她的遗愿
将她埋在了秘密地点
he buried her in a secret spot
at her request.
你只需要找出那个地方
All you need to do is find out where.
现在到处都是人
There's people everywhere.
继续走，没人会认出你来
Just keep walking.
No one knows it's you.
卡蜜
Cami.
我们得离开这条街
We have to get off this street.
如果发现什么情况，基兰会打给我
Kieran is gonna call me first
if he hears anything.
你们俩看起来很悠闲嘛
Well, you two look rather cozy.
没有，我刚跟以利亚说我们在浪费时间
Hardly. I was just telling Elijah
how we're wasting time.
你不喜欢节日庆典吗？
You don't like festivals?
为什么不呢？
I don't see why not?
谁会不喜欢街头市集？
Who doesn't love a street fair?
妹妹，你是来帮我们找人的吗？
Sister, come to help us
find our stray?
总不能让你的秘密武器
落到别人手里，对吧？
We can't let your secret weapon
get in the wrong hands, can we?
声明一下，我们很快就会找到她
For the record, we are
moments away from retrieving her.
你这语气我很熟悉呢，尼克劳斯
I recognize that tone of voice, Niklaus.
显然你又有阴谋诡计了
Clearly, you have some
diabolical machination.
是什么？
What is it?
提摩西
Timothy.
我能跟你聊聊吗？
Might I have a word?
卡蜜，是我，又来骚扰你了
Cami, hey, it's me.
Again. Stalking you.
我只是想知道你们在哪
Just really need to know
where you guys are,
这样才能在日出前跟你们会合
so I can meet you before
the sun comes up, again.
（未知来电）
喂？
Uh, hello?
约书亚，最让我失望的奴才
Joshua, my most
disappointing minion,
如果是我打给你，你应该不会接
I suspected you wouldn't answer
the call were it from me.
克劳斯，你好吗？
Klaus, hey, what up?
你猜怎么着？我搬来土耳其了
Guess what?
I just moved to Turkey.
很奇怪，土耳其人居然不吃火鸡
奇怪吧
Weirdly, they don't eat turkey here.
Go figure.
你在撒谎
You're lying.
实际上，我跟马赛尔刚刚还在说
In fact, Marcel and I were just
chatting about your failed
你这个双面间谋已经暴露
我们推测你应该
double-agent status,
and we've surmised that you're likely
还在城里，而且跟一个朋友在一起
still in town
and in the company of a friend.
一个年轻愤怒的女巫
Ayoung, angry witch.
不，不，这里没有女巫
不过火鸡很好吃
Uh, nope. No witches here.
Totally digging Turkey, though.
你确定要让黛维娜的
小提琴手真爱提摩西
Are you really gonna leave Davina's
fiddler soulmate, Timothy,
跟我独处吗？
alone with me?
小约
Oh, Josh.
她会怎么想呢？
What would she think of that?
我保证我只是想跟她聊聊
I assure you,
I just want to talk to her.
我跟提姆在宅邸那边等你
Tim and I will be at the compound.
我真希望她快点回家
I really do hope she comes home soon.
我们应该继续走
We should keep moving.
要等多久？
How long do we have to wait?
等几分钟吧
然后我去看看海岸是否安全
Give it a few minutes.
Then I'll check to see if the coast is clear.
小约，抱歉没接到你的电话
(PHONE BEEPS)
Josh, sorry I missed your calls.
什么？
What?
我不想告诉你的，但我了解克劳斯
I didn't want to tell you,
but I know Klaus.
如果黛维娜不出现，他会杀了提姆
If Davina doesn't show up,
he'll kill Tim.
我们会想办法的
We'll think of something.
你去法语区，注意别被发现
Make your way to the Quarter.
Stay hidden.
我们想到办法会传简讯给你
We'll text you when we have a plan.
(CELL PHONE BEEPS)
- 我要去找他
- 黛维娜，等等
-I have to go.
-Davina, wait.
我不能让提姆死
I can't let Tim die.
怎么了？
What's wrong?
那些女巫
The witches.
(DOOR OPENS)
不！
No!
卡蜜？
Cami?
我只是去拿几件衣服
I'm just grabbing some clothes.
给我两分钟，好吗？
Give me two minutes, please?
莎莉丝特让我着迷
ELlJAH: Celeste entrances me.
她完美无瑕
She is perfection.
她死了
She is dead.
即使太阳升起，我眼中只有黑夜
Even as the sun rises,
I see only night.
但我向她保证过
如果她死了
But for the promise
I made to her, that in death
我会将她葬在远离一切混乱的地方
I would bury her far
from the mayhem of witches,
远离女巫、吸血鬼，以及人类
vampires, and men.
对不起，以利亚
I'm so sorry, Elijah.
别紧张，是我，别对我出手
Hey. It's just me.
Don't, like, melt me.
你怎么在这里？
你应该躲起来的
What are you doing?
You're supposed to be hidden.
是的，你不也一样吗？
但你那一脸
So are you. Remember?
But you're kind of working that
“我要复仇”的表情让我十分担心
whole girl on a mission look
that makes me nervous.
你确定你要去招惹那个
Look, are you sure that you
really want to mess with
史上最坏的家伙吗？
the baddest dude
in all of history?
是他先带走提姆，招惹了我
He messed with me when he took Tim.
我要杀了他，杀了他们所有人
I'll kill him, all of them.
黛维娜，真祖是杀不死的
Davina, Originals can't be killed.
或许可以呢
Maybe they can.
我有着无穷的力量
我从未有像现在一样的感觉
I have so much power,
I've never felt anything like it before.
那些力量正在我体内增长积聚
It's growing, gathering inside me.
我很强大，小约
I'm strong, Josh.
- 如果你杀了他们，那么
- 什么？
-lf you kill them, then--
-What?
如果你真要这么做
就不要退缩
If you're gonna do it,
don't hold back.
用你所有的力量对付他们
You hit them with all you got.
真成人啊
你没告诉黛维娜如果她杀了克劳斯
That was very sweet, not telling Davina
that if she kills Klaus
你也会死，真是太高尚了
you die, too.
Very noble.
问题是，如果她真要去找我哥哥算帐
Problem is,
if she goes after my brother,
死的人会是她
she'll be the one who ends up dead.
这注定是个悲剧，送死也就没必要了
A very unnecessary end
to an already tragic story.
或许你愿意助我一臂之力帮帮她
Perhaps you'd like to help me help her.
蕾贝卡去哪了？
Where's Rebekah gotten off to?
我倒不担心蕾贝卡
It's not Rebekah that
I'm concerned about.
你怎么确定黛维娜一定会来？
And how are you be so
certain that Davina will come?
这么说会让别人以为你已经忘记了
One might think you've forgotten
what it's like to be in the grip
深陷在疯狂的迷恋中不能自拔的感觉
她会来的
of an all-consuming infatuation.
She'll come.
有必要搞得那么悲情吗，尼克劳斯？
Are the maudlin theatrics
absolutely necessary, Niklaus?
有道理
(VlOLlN PLAYlNG)
It's a fair point.
提摩西，能换首欢快点的曲子吗？
Timothy, play something
a little more upbeat, please.
真是个好孩子
That's a good lad.
派你去传个话，去得还真是久啊
Took you long enough
to spread the word.
你见过他的夜行者吗？
Have you met his Nightwalkers?
都不太灵光
Not the brightest assortment.
不管怎样，我都办妥了
All that matters is I got it covered.
黛维娜来了以后
你们俩要让我跟她谈
When Davina gets here, you two
need to let me do the talking.
你会有机会的
Well, I'm sure you'll have your chance.
你好，亲爱的
Hello, love.
沉默是金，谢谢你，提摩西
Silence is golden, Timothy.
Thank you.
黛维娜？
Davina?
我已经来了，让他下来
You got me here.
Now let him down.
我们得先谈谈关于你
回到我们身边的问题
Well, first, we have to have a little chat
about you returning to the fold.
我怎么跟你说的，克劳斯
让我来
What did I say, Klaus?
I got this.
小黛，发生什么事了？
D, what happened?
你为什么要逃走？
Why'd you run?
告诉我
我能帮你解决问题
Talk to me.
Hey, I can make it right.
怎么解决？威胁我的朋友吗？
How, by threatening my friend?
事实上那是我的主意
Actually, that was my idea.
我很抱歉
有时我为了表明立场做得有点过火
Apologies. I've been known to go
too far to make a point.
但这样确实很管用
But I do always get results.
你装出一副很自信的样子
但我知道真相
You pretend to be so confident,
but I know the truth.
你害怕大家看到你真正的一面
You're afraid everyone can see
what you really are.
一头野兽
An animal.
怪物
A beast.
为何不让我们看看你的真面目呢？
Why don't you show us your real face?
我受够你了
That's enough of you.
黛维娜，你不必这么做的
Davina, you don't have to do this.
你
You.
你当着我的面欺骗了我
You looked me in the eyes
and lied to my face.
假装你想要帮我
Pretended you wanted to help me.
听我说
Listen to me.
你自称是高尚的人
You call yourself the noble one,
但却跟你弟弟一样是个杀人凶手
but you're a killer
just like your brother.
一千年来，你以无辜人们的鲜血为食
For a thousand years,
you fed on innocent blood.
让你试试被鲜血噎死的滋味如何
Why don't you choke on it?
还有你
And you.
我曾那么信任你
I trusted you.
深爱着你
但你却只是利用我巩固你的势力
I loved you. But you were
just using me to stay in power.
你根本不关心我
You don't care about me.
你错了
You're wrong.
当你败给克劳斯
你就把我当作战利品给了他
When you lost to Klaus,
you handed me over like some trophy.
或许我该用铜锅煮了你
Maybe I should boil you in bronze.
我关心你
I care.
我视你如己出
I took you in like
you were my own blood.
不会吧，亲爱的
Come on now, love.
别跟我说你信他这一套
Don't tell me you were falling for that.
我们女孩们是不是该好好聊聊了？
Isn't it time for us girls
to have a chat?
这真是让人印象深刻
Now, that is impressive.
要我说，他们都罪有应得
And well-deserved, in my opinion.
在你对付我之前
我有个惊喜给你
Now, before you turn on me,
I have a surprise for you.
小约，你怎么来了？快走
Josh, what are you doing?
Get out of here.
你要干什么？
What are you doing?
如果我是克劳斯
我会将小约的头扭下来
Now, if I were Klaus,
I would rip Josh's head from his neck,
喂给夜行者
这将是你朋友的下场
feed it to a Nightwalker, and
that would be the end of your friend.
但伤害他人是男孩子才喜欢干的事
But hurting people is
such a boyish thing to do,
就像克劳斯如何魅惑那位
屋顶上的提琴手
Iike how Klaus compelled
your fiddler on the roof.
虽然我喜怒无常
但我绝对不像我哥哥
And, while I am many things,
I'm certainly not my brother.
没事了，提摩西，你可以下来了
没人会伤害你的
It's okay, Timothy. You can come down.
No one is going to hurt you.
他告诉我不能从横梁上爬下来
He told me I couldn't
climb down off this beam.
那就别用爬的，傻瓜
Then don't climb, silly.
我是这里唯一有脑子的吗？
跳啊
Am I the only smart one in the room?
Jump.
黛维娜，这些你是怎么做到的？
Davina, did you do all that?
我是怎么到这里的？
How did I even get here?
我会解释的，我保证
I'll explain everything, I promise.
你为什么这么做？
Why are you doing this?
在我看来，你掌控着整个局势
Seems to me that
you're the one holding all the cards,
但却不知道该相信谁
yet you don't know who to trust.
我向你证明了你可以相信我
I've just proven
that you can trust me.
现在我想再告诉你一件事
Now I'd like to show you
one more thing.
不会耽误很久
It won't take long.
你可以带着你的朋友
You can bring your friends.
苏菲，我把知道的都告诉你了
Sophie, I told you
everything that I found.
你说他把她埋在了
两棵可爱的橡树苗之间
You said he buried her
between two lovely oak saplings.
这已经是两百年前的事了
News flash, that was 200 years ago.
它们现在早就是大树了
They're all just trees now.
你想成为全能女巫，就继续找啊
You want to be the all-powerful witch,
keep looking.
做个祷告
Say a prayer.
有点信心
你可以的
Have a little faith.
You can do this.
好吧
(CELL PHONE BEEPS)
Okay.
拜托，请帮帮我
Please, please help me.
我在努力做正确的事
I'm trying to do the right thing.
别担心，他们不是真的死了
只是非常饿
Oh, don't worry. They're not really dead.
Just really hungry, and...
这样说也不会好点的
And I'm not helping.
你觉得我哥哥尼克很坏吗？
马赛尔算是得他真传了
You think my brother, Nik, is awful?
Marcel learned from the best.
他就是这样对待背叛他的
他所谓的朋友
This is how he treats his
so-called friends who betray him.
这里大部分可怜的家伙所做的
都不会比小约做的过分
Most of what these poor souls did
is no worse than what Josh did.
拿提艾里来说吧
Take Thierry, for example.
他曾是马赛尔最信任的朋友
He was Marcel's most trusted friend.
克劳斯设计让他
打破了马赛尔的一条规矩
Klaus tricked him into
breaking one of Marcel's rules.
马赛尔明知如此
还是把提艾里关在这里
Marcel knows this, and yet
he keeps Thierry locked in here
日复一日地受折磨
day after day suffering.
真是疯了
This is insane.
你为什么告诉我这些？
Why are you telling me this?
因为你得知道你要对付的是谁
Because you need to know
who you're dealing with,
谁是你可以信任的人
who you can trust.
嘿，嘿，没事的
Hey, hey.
It's gonna be okay.
你不会有事的
I mean, you know,
you're gonna be all right.
来
Here.
喝点水吧
Drink something.
黛维娜，你和我都被马赛尔和克劳斯
Davina, both you and
I have been lied to
欺骗和利用了
and taken advantage of
by Marcel and Klaus.
也许我们联手能够给他们小小的报复
Maybe together,
we can get a little payback.
提姆？
Tim?
是克劳斯
It was Klaus.
他逼我这么做的
He made me do it.
我之前都不知道自己在做什么
直到我让你…
I didn't even know what I was
doing until I made you...
让她什么？
Made her what?
喝水
Drink.
- 提姆？
- 克劳斯在水里下毒了
-Tim?
-Klaus poisoned the water.
提姆？
Tim?
黛维娜
Davina.
不
Oh, no.
卡蜜，你还好吗？
Cami, are you all right?
今天吃饭了吗？
Did you eat today?
你一定是昏过去了
Oh, you must have fainted.
是啊，或许我就是神秘地
被四个女巫弄昏了
Yeah, or I got mystically
cold-cocked by four witches.
黛维娜在哪？
Where's Davina?
你朋友马赛尔知道她在这里吗？
Does your friend, Marcel,
know she's here?
卡蜜，我可以解释
Cami, I can explain.
吸血鬼？女巫？
Vampires? Witches?
我的哥哥，你的侄子，被女巫下了咒
My brother, your nephew,
hexed by a witch.
你怎么能瞒着我？
How could you not tell me?
这很复杂
It's complicated.
有很多事情你不明白
There's a lot you don't understand.
你对我隐瞒真相
You hid the truth from me.
你让我相信西恩疯了
You let me believe
that Sean was crazy,
我疯了
而不是告诉我真相
that I was crazy,
instead of telling me the truth.
我是在保护你
I was protecting you.
你也看到西恩的下场了
卡蜜，拜托
You saw what happened to Sean.
Cami, please!
离我远点
Get the hell away from me.
你和这个城市里其他的怪物一样坏
You are every bit as bad
as the other monsters in this city.
是不是非常尴尬呢？
Isn't this monumentally awkward?
蕾贝卡，你在哪？
Rebekah, where are you?
我和黛维娜在一起，她快死了
都是因为你的背叛
I'm with Davina, and
she's dying because of your treachery.
出于对马赛尔的尊重，我曾试着跟她谈
Well, I tried to talk to her,
out of respect for Marcel,
但她明确表示她不是我们的朋友
but she made it quite clear
she is not our friend.
你若觉得她是你的朋友，我向你道歉
My apologies if you
thought she was yours.
告诉我要怎么救她
Just tell me how to cure her.
吸血鬼的血没有用
Vampire blood isn't working.
对，不会有用的
No. It wouldn't.
我魅惑提姆给她喝下的毒药
是非常有效的
You see, the poison I compelled
Timothy to feed her is quite potent.
她死只是早晚的问题了
It's just a matter of time for her.
是他们俩，你这个残忍的混蛋
For both of them,
you diabolical bastard.
他们还是孩子
They're children.
我们本来可以公平地和她做交易
We could've dealt with her fairly.
对于威胁我们的人，不用谈什么交易
There is no dealing with
those who threaten us.
黛维娜与我对立的那一刻开始
命运就已定
Davina sealed her fate
when she stood against me.
这是她的选择，不是我的
This was her choice, not mine.
(CELL PHONE BEEPS)
别这样
(CHUCKLlNG)
Oh, come on.
你们指责我的恶臭真是势不可档
The stench of your judgment
is overwhelming.
需要我提醒你们
黛维娜刚打败了我们吗？
Need I remind you that
Davina just bested the lot of us?
我只是做了该做的
I did what had to be done.
别担心，以利亚
Don't worry, Elijah.
我还是一如既往可被挽救
I remain as redeemable as ever.
所以你魅惑那个男孩去给黛维娜下毒
So you compelled that boy
to poison Davina
都不问问我和马赛尔
without consulting Marcel or myself.
你知道最糟糕的问题是什么吗？
You know what the worst part is?
是你太容易被看穿了
It's that you're so predictable,
我不得不与你哥哥结盟
我根本不喜欢他
I had to make an alliance with your
brother, who I don't even like.
听你的口气
你似乎有什么事想跟我说
Judging by your expression,
you have something you'd like to share.
你说对了
Damn straight, I do.
基兰稍早打了电话给我
就在莎宾和其他女巫
I got a call from Kieran earlier,
right after Sabine and some witches
对黛维娜下手之后
almost got their hands on Davina first.
你好啊
Oh, hello.
让我猜猜，保护咒吗？
Let me guess, protection spell?
你觉得我会白白浪费能施魔法的一天
什么都不做吗？
You think I'd let a day where witches
can do magic pass by without one?
她们本该都这么做的
They all should've done the same.
是啊
Yeah.
你违反了我的规矩，莎宾
我猜你的保护咒
You broke one of my rules, Sabine,
and I'm guessing that spell of yours
应该是一次性的吧
is probably a one-time deal.
我给你两个选择
I'll give you two choices.
你可以立刻和你天人永隔的朋友相见
An immediate reunion
with your dearly departed friends,
也可以为我的一个小女巫朋友
施同样的保护咒
or you can do that same spell
for a young witch friend of mine.
你大概知道我在说谁
Yeah, you probably know
which one I'm talking about.
所以你声称去看夜行者时
So, when you slipped away to
allegedly check on your Nightwalkers,
其实是在与一名女巫共谋
you were, in fact,
colluding with a witch.
很聪明嘛
Very clever.
我应该感到自豪
I suppose I should be proud.
我是想确保万无一失
I just wanted to make sure
I had a failsafe just in case,
正如以利亚所料，你开始露出本性
as Elijah expected,
you started acting like you.
但这次你选择了与女巫结盟
Except that now you've
involved the witches,
而据我所知
女巫一直是我们的敌人
who, last time I checked,
were enemy to us all,
对于我们的家人和一切都是威胁
to everything we have,
and to our family.
黛维娜就是马赛尔的家人，尼克劳斯
Davina is Marcel's family, Niklaus,
但你居然想取她性命
难道你忘了这一点吗？
or did that somehow slip your mind
as you tried to take her life?
打给蕾贝卡
You will call Rebekah.
告诉她黛维娜会恢复
You'll tell her that Davina will recover.
可惜那个男孩活不了了
I do wish the same could be said
for that boy.
提姆
Tim.
提姆，提姆
Tim? Tim.
提姆，提姆，醒醒
Tim, wake up.
提姆，快醒醒
Tim, please wake up.
睁开眼睛
Open your eyes.
不要啊，不要
No, no.
快醒来
Please wake up.
别丢下我一个人
Please don't leave me alone.
她还好吗？
Is she okay?
她情绪崩溃，疲惫不堪
She's devastated and exhausted.
她的房间在哪里？
Where's her room?
不用，我来就行
No, I got her.
交给我吧
I got her.
有人说，这是男人的世界
HAYLEY: It is said that
this is a man's world.
有时候的确是这样
And sometimes it is.
虽然很多木匣女孩被解救
但那毕竟是有限的
For every Casket Girl that was saved,
countless others were not.
她永远不会再信任我了
She'll never trust me again.
也许吧
Perhaps.
但你永远不能放弃重新争取她的信任
You must never surrender
the fight to reclaim that trust.
但女人其实比世人想像的更坚韧
HAYLEY: But women are more
resilient than given credit for.
这些画，是什么？
These drawings, what are they?
她在阁楼时就一直画这些
She drew those the whole time
she was in the attic,
她感受到魔法时，画出来的就不一样
said they're different than what
she draws when she senses magic.
这些，她称之为邪恶
These ones, she called them evil.
而有些女人呢
HAYLEY: And some women,
well...
这么说吧，曾欺压她们的人最好小心点
Let's just say, their oppressors
had better watch out.
见到我很惊讶吗？
Surprised to see me?
毕竟你曾魅惑我让我离开
After all, you did
compel me to leave town.
你记得了
You remember.
这都是解除魅惑的功劳
Chalk one up for de-compulsion.
虽然痛得要死，不过很值得
Hurts like hell, but it's worth it.
让我明白了为什么我想留下来
Made me realize exactly
why I want to stick around.
对了，克劳斯，如果你再敢
伤害戴维娜和小约
And Klaus, if you hurt
Davina or Josh in any way,
我会向全世界揭发你
I'll expose you to the world.
你就可以跟法语区吻别了
And then, you can kiss
the French Quarter goodbye.
永别
Forever.
晚安了
Have a nice night.
我也很坚韧
HAYLEY: I, too, am resilient.
我受够了被压迫
And I'm tired of being oppressed.
一千年来，我哥哥为了他想要的东西
不择手段
For a thousand years, my brother has
taken what he wants,
不计后果
in whatever way he wants,
regardless of the consequences.
马赛尔似乎已经默许
而以利亚也一直陪伴在他身旁
Marcel seems determined to allow it,
and Elijah stands right by his side
徒劳地等待着他某一天会改变
futilely awaiting
the day that he'll change.
男人很混蛋
So, men suck.
你想要我怎么做？
What do you want me to do about it?
虽然你警告过马赛尔
Despite your dire warnings to Marcel,
但他似乎无法放弃我哥哥
he just can't seem to quit my brother.
他们肩并肩
The two of them stand side by side,
统治着这个城市
却留你在这里腐烂
ruling this city
whilst you're left in here to rot.
我希望你帮我夺回纽奥良
I want you to help me take
New Orleans right out from
让他们眼睁睁看着
under all of their noses.
而且我有一个秘密武器
And I have something
they won't see coming,
一个内应
someone on the inside.
她自己也是个很坚韧的女孩
She's quite the resilient girl herself.
你还好吗？
You okay?
我现在好多了
I'm better now.
你今天过得如何？
How was your day?
棒极了
Killer.
这些画是什么？
What's with the artwork?
黛维娜的素描
Uh... Davina's sketches.
不知道是不是代表着什么预兆
I wonder if they represent
some kind of premonition.
好了
Okay.
似乎在暗示什么即将到来
They seem to suggest
something is coming.
似乎是凶兆
Something sinister.
我的天啊
Oh, my God.
那不是…
Isn't that...?
你好，莎莉丝特
Hello, Celeste.
快点，苏菲，快接电话
Come on, Sophie, pick up.
快点接啊
Pick up.
片名：创始吸血鬼（第一季）